servicecu.org 2003-06-18

# Service Credit Union

| 

| •  | Pay Your Bills  
---|---  
•  | Review Accounts  
•  | Transfer Funds  
•  | **It's Free**  

| 

Service Credit Union's Internet Privacy Statement

> Service Credit Union is committed to protecting member confidentiality and the privacy of each member's financial records consistent with state and federal laws. No personal information, such as your name or address, is collected by Service Credit Union. We collect no information which would identify you personally. Our servers collect standard non-identifying information about visits to this site, such as date and time visited, IP address, city, state, and country. This information is used to compile standard statistics on site usage. Service Credit Union does not give, sell or transfer personal information to third parties, unless required by law. When you send us personally identifying information, for example, in an electronic mail message containing a question or comment or by filling out a form that E-mails us this information, we use this information to fulfill or respond to your requests. We may store these requests to provide us with information for future improvements to our Web site. This information is never sold, given, or disclosed to third parties. To provide you with greater access of information, the Service Credit Union site also contains links to other sites. While we hope these organizations join us in respecting your privacy, Service Credit Union is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these other web sites. This privacy statement is for general guidance and does not constitute a contract or create legal rights and does not modify or amend any agreements we have with our members.
